<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pinnacle</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Pinnacle</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="aboutusheading">About Us</string>
    <string name="contactusphone">+919729327755</string>
    <string name="contectusemail">support@ssccglpinnacle.com</string>
    <string name="contectuswebsite">https://ssccglpinnacle.com/</string>
    <string-array name="header">
        <item>Welcome Into The Ocean of Knowledge</item>
        <item>Explore Your Skills</item>
        <item>And Assure Your Success&#8230;</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="quiz"><i>Which kind of waves are used to make and receive cellphone calls?</i></string>
    <string name="contactus"><b>Pinnacle Coaching Institute,\nGurudwara Road,\nNear Sharda Hospital,\nModel Town, Hisar, Haryana 125005</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus">Pinnacle coaching institute is founded by Baljit Dhaka and Neeru Madam in 2010 to provide high quality coaching to SSC CGL aspirants. To reach out plan,
        Pinnacle entered into Online Coaching for SSC CGL Since from inception Pinnacle is no 1 online coaching institute for SSC CGL across India.
        Having exposure and vast experience of corporate world by its founder directors Baljit Dhaka and Neeru madam,
        organization expended very fast and launched 80+ products for SSC CGL. To streamline and develop operational efficiency products range was redefined to make affordable.\n
    At present for SSC CGL Pinnacle have more than 2800+ videos. 1600+ E-booklets , 1000+ online tests, 500,000+ subscribers, 3000+ portal articles . 350,000 YouTube subscribers.\n
    Pinnacle is the only institute in India which provide online coaching for SSC CGL tier 3 and Tier 4.\n
    Pinnacle has developed specialized software for descriptive writing operation and skills test
    Pinnacle is the only institute in India providing online coaching for all tiers i.e. tier 1, tier 2, tier 3 and tier 4\n
    JobAssure is a famous brand of Pinnacle for tier 1, tier 2, tier 3 and tier 4 with videos solutions To handle relevant queries specially query box has been created for high value products.
    Pinnacle works through its virtual employees system and employees are working across India.
    Quality coaching at affordable price – Pinnacle is moving very fast.

    </string>
</resources>
